
      {
      
        "text": [
        "Start", 
        "How to play", 
        "Pick your player", 
        "Choose the correct answer.", 
        "Each time you catch a squid, you'll earn a coin.", 
        "But every time you get a question wrongâ€¦splat! Beware, you'll lose a life.", 
        "Play", 
        "Level", 
        "Play Again", 
        "Yay!", 
        "You've cleared this level.", 
        "You have done it.", 
        "Next Level"],
      
      "question": {
                   
                             "easy":[
                                   
                                   {
                                     "id":"1",
                                     "question":"the problem in a story",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "conflict",
                                        "character",
                                        "resolution"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "conflict"

                                   },
                                   {
                                     "id":"2",
                                     "question":"a word that means the opposite",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "antonym",
                                        "synonym",
                                        "definition"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "antonym"

                                   },
                                   {
                                     "id":"3",
                                     "question":"a rock that circles the Sun",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "asteroid",
                                        "moon",
                                        "spacecraft"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "asteroid"

                                   },
                                   {
                                     "id":"4",
                                     "question":"to do with the Sun",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "solar",
                                        "lunar",
                                        "astral"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "solar"

                                   },
                                   {
                                     "id":"5",
                                     "question":"materials, on on top of another",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "layers",
                                        "mixture",
                                        "fabric"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "layers"

                                   },
                                   {
                                     "id":"6",
                                     "question":"Emma travels through the Solar __.",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "System",
                                        "Galaxy",
                                        "Orbit"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "System"

                                   },
                                   {
                                     "id":"7",
                                     "question":"the antonym of smooth",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "bumpy",
                                        "soft",
                                        "amazing"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "bumpy"

                                   },
                                   {
                                     "id":"8",
                                     "question":"the antonym of massive",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "tiny",
                                        "little",
                                        "big"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "tiny"

                                   },
                                   {
                                     "id":"9",
                                     "question":"Jupiter's red spot is a __.",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "storm",
                                        "crater",
                                        "lake"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "storm"

                                   },
                                   {
                                     "id":"10",
                                     "question":"The surface of Jupiter is a __.",
                                     "options":[
                                     
                                        "gas",
                                        "solid",
                                        "liquid"
                                     ],
                                    "correct":  "gas"

                                   }

                                ]
                          
                }
        }        

    